https://www.allaboutwicker.com/store/privacy.php?osCsid=51e8860815925b04460f7a2b8ecde48e

Categories
Outdoor Wicker Furniture Outdoor Wicker FurnitureOutdoor Wicker SetsOutdoor Wicker Dining SetsWicker Chairs & RockersWicker Swings and GlidersSmall Tables & OttomansBainbridge Outdoor WickerCharleston Outdoor WickerMackinac Wicker FurnitureCabo Outdoor Wicker FurnitureSt Lucia Wicker FurnitureNantucket Outdoor WickerSavannah Outdoor WickerRegatta Outdoor WickerSummerset Outdoor WickerWinward Outdoor WickerSt Thomas Outdoor WickerRiviera Outdoor WickerTisdale Outdoor WickerIndoor Wicker Furniture Indoor Wicker FurnitureAruba Rattan CollectionCape Cod Wicker CollectionGrand Cayman WickerPapasan Rattan CollectionSeagull Wicker CollectionWicker and Rattan SetsWicker Sofas, Chairs, RockersWicker Tables & OttomansFurniture Cushions Furniture CushionsFurniture CushionsThrow PillowsBedroom Furniture Bedroom FurnitureBombay Wicker Rattan BedroomFlorentine Wicker Bedroom CollectionHampton Bay Wicker Bedroom CollectionLivingston Wicker Bedroom CollectionWicker and Rattan HeadboardsWicker Bedroom Dressers and ChestsWicker Nightstands & AccessoriesWicker Dining FurnitureWicker MirrorsWicker AccessoriesWicker Office FurnitureCarts, Shelves, TV StandsWicker Bars - StoolsFurniture CoversSpecials and Clearance
Home
Privacy Notice
Privacy Notice
Privacy Notice
This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which All About Wicker collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the allaboutwicker.com website ("Site"). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by All About Wicker.
Personal identification information
We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, place an order and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, mailing address, phone number, credit card information. Users may however, visit our site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.
Non-personal identification information
We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.
Web browser cookies
Our Site may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. Users web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.
How we use collected information
All About Wicker collects and uses Users personal information for the following purposes:
To improve customer service - Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.
To personalize user experience - We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.
To improve our Site - We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.
To process transactions - We may use the information Users provide about themselves when placing an order only to provide service to that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to provide the service.
To send periodic emails - The email address Users provide for order processing, will only be used to send them information and updates pertaining to their order. It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, and/or other requests or questions. If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email or User may contact us via our Site.
How we protect your information
We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site. Sensitive and private data exchange between the Site and its Users happens over a SSL secured communication channel and is encrypted and protected with digital signatures. Our Site is also in compliance with PCI vulnerability standards in order to create as secure of an environment as possible for Users.
Changes to this privacy policy
All About Wicker has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, revise the updated date at the bottom of this page,. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.
Your acceptance of these terms
By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy and terms of service. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.
Contacting us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us by emailing us at allaboutwicker@gmail.com or by calling 1-866-594-2537.
Continue
Collections
Please SelectAruba Rattan CollectionBainbridge Wicker CollectionBermuda Rattan CollectionBombay Wicker Bedroom CollectionCabo Wicker CollectionCape Cod CollectionCharleston Wicker CollectionFlorentine Wicker BedroomGrand Cayman Wicker CollectionHanover Wicker Bedroom FurnitureLivingston Wicker BedroomMackinac Wicker CollectionNantucket Outdoor WickerPapasan Rattan CollectionRegatta Wicker CollectionReplacement Furniture CushionsRiviera Wicker CollectionSavannah Outdoor WickerSeagull Indoor CollectionSt Lucia Wicker CollectionSt Thomas Wicker CollectionSummerset Wicker FurnitureTisdale Outdoor WickerWinward Wicker Collection
Information
Shipping & Returns
Privacy Notice
Conditions of Use
Contact Us
Fabric Charts
Site Map
Categories
Outdoor Wicker FurnitureIndoor Wicker FurnitureFurniture CushionsBedroom FurnitureWicker Dining FurnitureWicker MirrorsWicker AccessoriesWicker Office FurnitureCarts, Shelves, TV StandsWicker Bars - StoolsFurniture CoversSpecials and Clearance
Quick Find
Use keywords to find the product you are looking for.Advanced Search
Reviews
Order this after the help of Leslie (thank you! Great Servic...
Specials
Tisdale Outdoor Wicker Storage End Table$349.00$195.00
